<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>data on Rami Krispin</title>
    <link>/tags/data/</link>
    <description>Recent content in data on Rami Krispin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>covid19italy v0.3.0 is now on CRAN</title>
      <link>/2020/07/covid19italy-v0-3-0-is-now-on-cran/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/07/covid19italy-v0-3-0-is-now-on-cran/</guid>
      <description>Version 0.3.0 of the covid19italy is now available on CRAN. The package provides a daily snapshot of the covid19 cases in Italy by province, region and national levels. While the data on the package is getting refreshed once every few months, the update_data function enables you to get the most recent data available on the Github version (updated on a daily basis).
Additional resources:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>coronavirus v0.2.0 is now on CRAN</title>
      <link>/2020/05/coronavirus-v0-2-0-is-now-on-cran/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/05/coronavirus-v0-2-0-is-now-on-cran/</guid>
      <description>Version 0.2.0 of the coronavirus R data package was pushed today to CRAN. The coronavirus package provides a tidy format for Johns Hopkins University Center for Systems Science and Engineering (JHU CCSE) Coronavirus dataset. Version 0.2.0 catch up with the significant changes in the data that took place since the initial release on February 24, changing the package status from experimental to maturing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>covid19italy v0.2.0 is now on CRAN</title>
      <link>/2020/05/covid19italy-v0-2-0-is-now-on-cran/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/05/covid19italy-v0-2-0-is-now-on-cran/</guid>
      <description>Last week I pushed an update of the covid19italy package to CRAN (v0.2.0). The covid19italy R package provides a tidy format dataset of the 2019 Novel Coronavirus COVID-19 (2019-nCoV) pandemic outbreak in Italy. The package includes the following three datasets:
 italy_total - daily summary of the outbreak on the national level italy_region - daily summary of the outbreak on the region level italy_province - daily summary of the outbreak on the province level  More details about the datasets available on the following vignette</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>